George F. Aker Papers
George F. Aker Papers
- National Seminar on Adult Education Research
  - Annual meetings, 1961-1968; 8 folders (Box 7)
Boyd, Robert D. - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Correspondence, general 1968 Nov. 4 (box 1) 1969 Feb. 18 (box 1) (2 letters) 1969 Oct. 2 (box 1) 1970 Feb. 10 (box 1) 1970 Mar. 3 (box 1) 1970 Mar. 4 (box 1) 1970 Apr. 23 (box 1) 1970 May 6 (box 1) 1970 Jul. 20 (box 1)
Boyd, Robert D. - Florida State University / Correspondence 1967 Jan. 25 (box 5) 1967 Mar. 8 (box 5) 1967 May 25 (box 5) 1967 May 30 (box 5) 1967 Dec. 20 (box 5) 1968 Jan. 21 (box 5) 1968 Jul. 1 (box 5) 1968 Jul. 10 (box 2) 1968 Aug. 2 (box 5) 1968 Nov. 13 (box 2)
Carlson, Robert A. - Florida State University / Correspondence 1968 Jan. 15 (box 5) 1968 Feb. 14 (box 2) 1968 Mar. 8 (box 2) 1968 Mar. 22 (box 5) 1969 Feb. 9 (box 5)
Charters, Alexander N. * - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Correspondence, general 1969 Dec. 30 (box 1)
Charters, Alexander N. * - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Handbook of Adult Education / Correspondence 1968 Jul. 12 (box 2) 1968 Aug. 6 (box 2) 1968 Nov. 4 (box 2) 1968 Dec. 21 (box 2) 1969 Feb. 5 (box 2) 1969 Feb. 13 (box 2) 1969 Apr. 1 (box 2) 1969 Apr. 22 (box 2) 1969 Oct. 6 (box 2)
Charters, Alexander N. * - Florida State University / Correspondence 1969 Sep. 19 (box 5) 1969 Oct. 14 (box 2) 1969 Oct. 30 (box 5) 1972 Mar. 6 (box 6) 1973 Sep. 13 (box 6) 1973 Sep. 26 (box 3) 1973 Nov. 2 (box 3) 1973 Nov. 16 (box 6) 1973 Nov. 26 (box 6) 1974 Jan. 11 (box 6) (2 letters) 1976 Aug. 11 (box 6) 1977 Jan. 24 (box 4) 1978 Mar. 20 (box 4) 1978 Apr. 2 (box 6) 1981 Dec. (box 4) 1982 Jul. 1 (box 4)
Fling, James H. - Florida State University / Correspondence 1965 Jun. 17 (box 5) 1967 Sep. 15 (box 5) 1968 May 6 (box 2) 1968 May 9 (box 5) 1968 May 10 (box 5) 1968 May 15 (box 2) 1968 Jun. 24 (box 2) 1968 Jun. 28 (box 5) 1968 Jul. 3 (box 5) 1968 Jul. 18 (box 5) 1968 Aug. 2 (box 5) 1968 Dec. 18 (box 5) 1969 Jan. 6 (box 2) 1969 Jan. 10 (box 5) 1969 Mar. 21 (box 2) 1969 Mar. 31 (box 5) 1969 Apr. 4 (box 2) 1969 May 27 (box 5) 1969 Jun. 23 (box 5) 1969 Jul. 7 (box 5) 1969 Jul. 11 (box 2) 1969 Nov. 5 (box 5) 1970 Feb. 2 (box 5) 1970 Mar. 24 (box 2) 1970 May 25 (box 5) 1970 Jun. 16 (box 5) 1970 Jul. 3 (box 2) 1970 Aug. 2 (box 2)6 1971 Mar. 19 (box 2) 1971 Jun. 23 (box 5) 1972 Mar. 24 (box 6) 1972 Jun. 1 (box 6) (2 letters) 1972 Jul. 5 (box 6) 1972 Jul. 24 (box 6) 1972 Oct. 30 (box 3) 1973 Jan. 19 (box 3) 1973 Feb. 14 (box 3) 1973 Feb. 17 (box 6) 1973 Aug. 16 (box 6) 1973 Aug. 22 (box 3) 1973 Aug. 28 (box 6) 1974 Mar. 25 (box 3) 1975 Jan. 15 (box 6) 1975 May 14 (box 4) 1975 May 16 (box 4) 1976 Jul. 19 (box 6) 1976 Oct. 26 (box 6) 1978 Apr. 12 (box 4) 1978 May 9 (box 6) 1980 Apr. 8 (box 4) 1981 Sep. 9 (box 4) 1983 Jan. 25 (box 4)
Fling, James H. - Florida State University / Institute on Education for Older Citizens / Correspondence 1968 May 2 (box 7) 1968 May 20 (box 7) 1968 Jun. 7 (box 7) 1971 Feb. 1 (box 7) 1971 Mar. 30 (box 7) 1971 Apr. 5 (box 7) 1972 Mar. 10 (box 7) 1972 May 17 (box 7) 1974 Apr. 23 (box 7) 1974 May 8 (box 7)
Friere, Paulo - Florida State University / Correspondence 1976 Aug. 18 (box 6)
Hendrickson, Andrew * - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Handbook of Adult Education / Correspondence 1968 Jul. 24 (box 2) 1969 Feb. 13 (box 2) 1969 Jun. 4 (box 2) 1969 Oct. 6 (box 2)
Hendrickson, Andrew * - Florida State University / Correspondence 1965 Feb. 5 (box 2) 1965 Mar. 10 (box 2) 1965 Mar. 24 (box 2) 1967 Feb. 22 (box 5) 1967 Apr. 26 (box 5) 1967 Aug. 21 (box 5) 1967 Sep. 19 (box 5) 1968 Feb. 14 (box 5) 1968 Apr. 3 (box 5) 1968 Aug. 1 (box 5) 1969 Apr. 15 (box 2) 1969 May 7 (box 5) 1969 Jun. 12 (box 5) 1969 Sep. 22 (box 5) 1969 Sep. 26 (box 5) 1970 Jan. 13 (box 5) (2 letters) 1970 Feb. 11 (box 5) 1970 Mar. 19 (box 2) 1970 Apr. 3 (box 5) 1970 May 28 (box 2) 1970 Jun. 8 (box 2) 1970 Jun. 12 (box 5) 1970 Jun. 16 (box 5) 1970 Jul. 20 (box 5) 1970 Sep. 14 (box 5) 1970 Sep. 15 (box 2) 1970 Sep. 29 (box 5) 1970 Oct. 9 (box 5) 1970 Nov. 3 (box 5) 1970 Nov. 24 (box 5) 1970 Dec. 2 (box 5) (2 letters) 1971 Feb. 22 (box 2) 1971 Mar. 18 (box 2) 1971 Mar. 29 (box 2) 1971 Apr. 7 (box 2) 1971 Jun. 23 (box 5) 1971 Sep. 27 (box 5) 1972 Jan. 5 (box 3) 1972 Apr. 6 (box 3) 1972 Apr. 24 (box 3) 1972 May 3 (box 5) 1972 May 4 (box 3) 1972 Jul. 17 (box 5) 1972 Aug. 10 (box 3) 1972 Aug. 24 (box 3) 1972 Dec. 1 (box 3) 1972 Dec. 14 (box 3) 1973 Jan. 12 (box 5) 1973 Jul. 3 (box 3) 1973 Jul. 13 (box 3) 1973 Jul. 13 (box 5) 1974 Jun. 4 (box 3) 1973 Sep. 6 (box 5) 1974 Jan. 7 (box 5) 1974 Jul. (box 5) 1975 Feb. 25 (box 5) 1976 Feb. 19 (box 5)
Houle, Cyril O. * - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Commission of Professors of Adult Education / Correspondence 1966 Dec. 1 (box 1)
Houle, Cyril O. * - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Correspondence, general 1968 Oct. 7 (box 1)
Houle, Cyril O. * - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Handbook of Adult Education / Correspondence 1968 Jul. 12 (box 2) 1968 Sep. 27 (box 2) 1968 Nov. 4 (box 2) 1968 Dec. 27 (box 2) (2 letters) 1969 Jan. 6 (box 2) 1969 Feb. 5 (box 2) 1969 Feb. 14 (box 2) 1969 Jul. 1 (box 2) 1969 Jul. 11 (box 2) 1969 Jul. 29 (box 2) 1969 Oct. 6 (box 2)
Houle, Cyril O. * - Florida State University / Correspondence 1963 Oct. 3 (box 5) 1963 Oct. 14 (box 2) 1963 Nov. 26 (box 5) 1963 Nov. 29 (box 5) 1963 Dec. 19 (box 2) 1964 Jan. 6 (box 5) 1964 Jun. 10 (box 2) 1965 Feb. 5 (box 2) 1965 Mar. 4 (box 2) 1965 Mar. 9 (box 2) 1965 Mar. 16 (box 5) 1965 Mar. 18 (box 2) 1965 Apr. 13 (box 5) 1965 May 3 (box 2) 1965 May 11 (box 5) 1965 Jul. 16 (box 5) 1965 Jul. 8 (box 2) 1965 Nov. 3 (box 2)0 1965 Dec. 10 (box 5) 1968 Dec. 12 (box 2) 1965 Dec. 22 (box 5) 1967 Aug. 31 (box 5) 1967 Dec. 18 (box 5) 1968 Oct. 15 (box 5) 1968 Oct. 23 (box 5) 1969 May 22 (box 5) 1969 Jul. 14 (box 2) 1969 Aug. 6 (box 2) 1969 Sep. 29 (box 2) 1969 Sep. 19 (box 5) 1969 Oct. 14 (box 2) 1970 Jan. 16 (box 5) 1970 Feb. 24 (box 5) 1970 Dec. 1 (box 2) 1970 Dec. 7 (box 5) 1971 Feb. 3 (box 5) 1971 Feb. 25 (box 2) 1971 Mar. 5 (box 5) 1971 Apr. 1 (box 2) 1971 Oct. 28 (box 2) 1972 Dec. 20 (box 6) 1973 Jan. 3 (box 3) 1975 Jun. 13 (box 4) 1975 Jun. 20 (box 6) 1976 May 18 (box 6)
Humphrey, Sen. Hubert H. - Florida State University / Institute on Education for Older Citizens / Correspondence 1972 Feb. 29 (box 7)
Jackson, Sen. Henry - Florida State University / Institute on Education for Older Citizens / Correspondence 1972 Jan. 26 (box 7)
Jacques, Joseph L. * - Florida State University / Correspondence 1972 Mar. 23 (box 6) 1972 Apr. 17 (box 3) 1973 Jul. 2 (box 3) 1973 Aug. 2 (box 3)2 1973 Aug. 16 (box 6) 1973 Sep. 11 (box 6) 1973 Oct. 22 (box 3) 1974 Jan. 31 (box 3) 1974 May (box 3) 1976 May 13 (box 6) (2 letters) 1976 Oct. 26 (box 4) 1977 Sep. 20 (box 4) 1977 Sep. 30 (box 6) 1977 Oct. 13 (box 4)
Jacques, Joseph L. * - Florida State University / Institute on Education for Older Citizens / Correspondence 1974 May 16 (box 7)
Javits, Sen. Jacob - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Correspondence, general 1971 Feb. 11 (box 1)
Johnson, Eugene I. - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Correspondence, general 1968 Feb. 21 (box 1) 1968 Jul. 2 (box 1) 1968 Jul. 11 (box 1) 1968 Jul. 15 (box 1) 1968 Jul. 18 (box 1) 1968 Aug. 7 (box 1) 1968 Aug. 14 (box 1) (2 letters) 1968 Aug. 27 (box 1) 1969 Apr. 30 (box 1)
Johnson, Eugene I. - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Handbook of Adult Education / Correspondence 1968 Apr. 9 (box 2) (2 letters) 1968 Apr. 24 (box 2) 1968 Apr. 30 (box 2) 1968 Jul. 1 (box 2) 1968 Jul. 11 (box 2) 1968 Aug. 5 (box 2) 1968 Sep. 20 (box 2) 1968 Nov. 4 (box 2) 1968 Dec. 22 (box 2) 1969 Jan. 4 (box 2) 1969 Jan. 10 (box 2) 1969 Mar. 10 (box 2) 1969 Mar. 18 (box 2) 1969 Mar. 27 (box 2) 1969 Apr. 9 (box 2) 1969 Oct. 6 (box 2)
Johnson, Eugene I. - Florida State University / Correspondence 1964 Jun. 24 (box 2) 1967 Mar. 7 (box 5) 1967 Apr. 7 (box 5) 1967 May 30 (box 5) (2 letters) 1967 Jun. 1 (box 5) 1967 Jul. 3 (box 5) 1967 Jul. 18 (box 5) 1967 Jul. 24 (box 5) 1967 Aug. 8 (box 5) 1967 Sep. 11 (box 5) 1967 Oct. 24 (box 5) 1967 Dec. 6 (box 5) 1968 Jan. 24 (box 2) 1968 Jan. 31 (box 5) 1972 May 26 (box 3) 1968 Feb. 5 (box 5) 1968 Apr. 30 (box 5) 1968 May 8 (box 5) 1968 Jun. 25 (box 5) 1968 Jul. 1 (box 5) 1968 Jul. 11 (box 5) 1968 Jul. 18 (box 5) 1969 May 8 (box 5)
Johnson, Eugene I. - Florida State University / Institute on Education for Older Citizens / Correspondence 1974 Jun. 10 (box 7)
Kadir, Mohamed A. - Florida State University /. Correspondence 1968 Feb. 16 (box 5) 1972 Jun. 23 (box 6) 1972 Jul. 17 (box 3) 1972 Oct. 17 (box 3) 1972 Oct. 18 (box 6) 1973 Apr. 25 (box 6) (2 letters) 1973 May 11 (box 6) 1973 Aug. 10 (box 6) 1973 Sep. 6 (box 3) 1974 Jan. 7 (box 3) 1974 Jan. 11 (box 6) (2 letters) 1974 Feb. 6 (box 3) 1974 Jul. 16 (box 6) 1974 Nov. 21 (box 3) 1975 Jan. 9 (box 6) 1976 Mar. 23 (box 4) 1976 Apr. 7 (box 6) 1976 Sep. 28 (box 6) 1976 Oct. 5 (box 4) 1976 Oct. 28 (box 6) 1977 Mar. 29 (box 4) 1977 May 24 (box 6) 1977 May 27 (box 6) 1979 Dec. 21 (box 4) 1980 Apr. 1 (box 6)
Kapoor, Sudarshan - Florida State University / Correspondence 1967 Jan. 26 (box 5) 1967 Jun. 28 (box 5) 1967 Jul. 25 (box 5) 1967 Sep. 14 (box 5) 1967 Oct. 2 (box 5) 1967 Dec. 19 (box 5) 1968 Dec. 14 (box 2) 1969 Jan. 2 (box 5) 1969 Jan. 6 (box 2) 1969 Jan. 9 (box 2) 1969 Mar. 24 (box 2) 1969 Apr. 1 (box 5) 1969 Apr. 14 (box 2) 1969 Dec. 29 (box 2) 1970 Feb. 13 (box 5) 1970 Dec. 29 (box 2) 1971 Jan. 15 (box 5) 1972 Mar. 14 (box 3) 1972 Apr. 15 (box 3) 1972 May 15 (box 6) 1973 Aug. 16 (box 6) 1973 Sep. 5 (box 6) 1973 Dec. 14 (box 3)
Kempfer, Homer - Florida State University / Correspondence 1967 Apr. 25 (box 5) 1967 Aug. 29 (box 5) 1967 Oct. 16 (box 5) 1975 Jul. 23 (box 4) 1975 Jul. 24 (box 6) 1975 Jul. 29 (box 4) 1975 Jul. 30 (box 4) 1975 Aug. 4 (box 6)
Kidd, J. R. - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Commission of Professors of Adult Education / Correspondence 1967 Jan. 26 (box 1) 1967 Mar. 3 (box 1) 1967 Apr. 21 (box 1)
Kidd, J. R. - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Correspondence, general 1970 Jul. 13 (box 1) 1970 Jul. 23 (box 1) 1970 Jul. 30 (box 1) 1970 Aug. 13 (box 1)
Kidd, J. R. - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Handbook of Adult Education / Correspondence 1968 Jun. 20 (box 2) 1968 Sep. 20 (box 2) 1969 Jan. 14 (box 2) 1969 Sep. 19 (box 2) 1970 Mar. 17 (box 2)
Kidd, J. R. - Florida State University / Correspondence 1967 Jan. 26 (box 5) 1967 Apr. 21 (box 5) 1967 Dec. 14 (box 5) 1968 Mar. 28 (box 2) 1968 May 9 (box 5) 1968 Jun. 6 (box 2) 1968 Jun. 12 (box 5) 1968 Jul. 9 (box 5) 1969 Jun. 16 (box 2) 1969 Jul. 7 (box 5) 1969 Sep. 3 (box 2) 1970 Mar. 30 (box 5) 1970 Mar. 31 (box 2) 1970 Apr. 21 (box 2) 1970 Apr. 24 (box 5) 1970 Jun. 8 (box 2) 1970 Jun. 11 (box 2) 1970 Jun. 26 (box 5) 1970 Jul. 15 (box 5) 1970 Nov. 23 (box 5) 1972 Mar. 30 (box 6) 1972 Nov. 10 (box 3) 1972 Dec. 20 (box 6) 1973 Aug. 22 (box 6) 1973 Oct. 24 (box 3) 1974 Mar. 4 (box 3) 1974 May 24 (box 3) 1974 Nov. 18 (box 3) 1976 Mar. 23 (box 6) 1976 Apr. 6 (box 4) 1976 Apr. 23 (box 4) 1976 May 5 (box 4) 1976 May 31 (box 4) 1976 Jun. 16 (box 6) 1976 Jul. 29 (box 4) 1976 Nov. 25 (box 4) 1977 Nov. 18 (box 4)
Knowles, Malcolm S. * - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Commission of Professors of Adult Education / Correspondence 1965 Sep. 21 (box 1) 1966 May 5 (box 1) 1971 Oct. 13 (box 1)
Knowles, Malcolm S. * - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Handbook of Adult Education / Correspondence 1969 May 14 (box 2)
Knowles, Malcolm S. * - Florida State University / Correspondence 1965 Feb. 5 (box 2) 1965 Mar. 4 (box 2) 1967 May 4 (box 5) 1969 Jan. 2 (box 2) 1969 Jan. 24 (box 5) 1969 Nov. 18 (box 5) 1970 May 21 (box 5) 1972 Dec. 20 (box 6) 1973 Apr. 26 (box 6) (box 6) 1973 Jun. 11 (box 3) 1974 Apr. (box 3) 1974 Oct. 9 (box 3) 1975 Apr. (box 4) 1976 Jan. 16 (box 4) 1976 Dec. 3 (box 4) 1976 Dec. 17 (box 6) (2 letters) 1977 Jan. 5 (box 6) 1977 Jan. 17 (box 4) 1977 Feb. 3 (box 4) 1980 Jan. 16 (box 4) 1980 Apr. 1 (box 6)
Kreitlow, Burton W. - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Commission of Professors of Adult Education / Correspondence 1957 Jan. 29 (box 1) 1967 Mar. 20 (box 1) 1969 Jan. 24 (box 1) 1969 Aug. 14 (box 1)
Kreitlow, Burton W. - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Correspondence, general 1968 Nov. 23 (box 1)
Kreitlow, Burton W. - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Handbook of Adult Education / Correspondence 1968 Jul. 11 (box 2) 1968 Jul. 25 (box 2) 1968 Aug. 5 (box 2) 1968 Aug. 21 (box 2) 1968 Nov. 4 (box 2) 1968 Dec. 9 (box 2) 1968 Dec. 23 (box 2) 1968 Dec. 24 (box 2) 1969 Jan. 3 (box 2) 1969 Oct. 6 (box 2) 1970 Jan. 30 (box 2)
Kreitlow, Burton W. - Florida State University / Correspondence 1958 Jan. 7 (box 5) 1959 Jan. 20 (box 2) 1959 Apr. 21 (box 5) 1959 Jul. 10 (box 2) 1967 May 25 (box 5) 1967 Dec. 20 (box 5) 1968 Aug. 14 (box 5) 1969 Nov. 18 (box 5) 1970 Feb. 10 (box 5) 1970 May 25 (box 5) 1973 Apr. 4 (box 3) 1973 Nov. 13 (box 6) 1977 Mar. 17 (box 4) 1977 Mar. 28 (box 6) 1977 Apr. 26 (box 4) 1977 Jun. 6 (box 4) 1977 Jun. 19 (box 4) 1977 Jun. 23 (box 6)
Landau, Sol - Florida State University / Correspondence 1967 Aug. 31 (box 5) 1967 Sep. 19 (box 5) 1967 Dec. 20 (box 5) 1968 Mar. 7 (box 5) 1970 Apr. 14 (box 5) 1971 Mar. 18 (box 5) 1972 Jul. 9 (box 3) 1973 Aug. 10 (box 6) 1973 Aug. 16 (box 6) 1974 Jan. 16 (box 6) 1974 Oct. 24 (box 6) 1975 Jan. 14 (box 4) 1975 Jan. 20 (box 4) 1975 Feb. 25 (box 6) 1975 Mar. 14 (box 6) 1975 Jun. 11 (box 4) 1975 Jun. 20 (box 6) 1975 Sep. 2 (box 4) 1975 Sep. 12 (box 6) 1976 Jan. 22 (box 6) 1976 Apr. 6 (box 6) 1976 Apr. 13 (box 4) 1977 Mar. 7 (box 6) 1977 Mar. 19 (box 4) 1977 Jun. 27 (box 6) 1977 Aug. (box 4) 1977 Aug. 24 (box 6) (2 letters) 1977 Sep. 15 (box 4) 1978 Apr. 18 (box 4) 1979 Feb. 7 (box 4) 1980 Feb. 5 (box 4) 1981 Aug. 18 (box 4) 1981 Sep. 4 (box 6) 1982 Jun. 1 (box 4)
Law, David Kwok-Chuen - Florida State University 1967 Jan. 17 (box 5) 1967 Jan. 19 (box 5) 1967 Feb. 8 (box 5) 1967 Jun. 1 (box 5) 1967 Nov. 16 (box 5) 1967 Dec. 14 (box 5) 1968 Feb. 16 (box 5) 1968 Mar. 7 (box 5) 1968 May 7 (box 5) 1968 Jul. 18 (box 5) 1969 Feb. 24 (box 5) 1969 Aug. 6 (box 5) 1969 Oct. 21 (box 5) 1969 Nov. 7 (box 2) 1969 Dec. 2 (box 5) 1970 Mar. 2 (box 5) 1970 Mar. 13 (box 2) 1970 Jun. 16 (box 2) 1970 Jul. 20 (box 5) 1970 Oct. 19 (box 5) 1970 Nov. 20 (box 2) 1971 Jan. 13 (box 5) 1971 Dec. 28 (box 4) 1972 Mar. 30 (box 6) 1972 Nov. 2 (box 6) 1973 Feb. 15 (box 6) 1973 Apr. 27 (box 6) 1973 May 21 (box 6) 1973 Jun. 18 (box 6) 1973 Aug. 3 (box 6) 1974 Jul. 16 (box 6) 1974 Sep. 9 (box 6) 1975 Jan. 8 (box 6) 1975 Jun. 17 (box 4) 1975 Jul. 14 (box 6) 1975 Aug. 1 (box 4) 1975 Aug. 4 (box 4) 1975 Oct. 3 (box 4) 1975 Dec. 2 (box 4) 1976 Feb. 20 (box 4) 1976 Mar. 15 (box 6) 1976 Apr. 24 (box 4) 1976 May 7 (box 6) 1976 Aug. 9 (box 6) 1976 Aug. 24 (box 4) 1976 Sep. 20 (box 4) 1976 Dec. 10 (box 6) 1976 Dec. 14 (box 6) 1977 Jan. 10 (box 4) 1977 Feb. 1 (box 4) 1977 Feb. 7 (box 6) 1977 Mar. 6 (box 4) 1977 Mar. 15 (box 6) 1977 Jun. 7 (box 6) 1979 Feb. 6 (box 4) 1979 Mar. 14 (box 4) 1979 Jul. 20 (box 4) 1984 Jan. 12 (box 4)
Law, David Kwok-Chuen - Florida State University / Institute on Education for Older Citizens / Correspondence 1973 May 10 (box 7)
Liveright, A. A.* - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Commission of Professors of Adult Education / Correspondence 1965 Aug. 5 (box 1)
Liveright, A. A.* - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Florida State University / Correspondence 1965 Feb. 5 (box 2) 1965 Feb. 9 (box 2) (2 letters) 1965 Mar. 11 (box 5) 1967 Feb. 8 (box 5) 1967 Oct. 12 (box 5) 1967 Nov. 4 (box 5) 1968 Oct. 1 (box 2)
Long, Huey B. - Florida State University / Correspondence 1967 Jan. 11 (box 5) 1967 Jan. 25 (box 5) 1967 Feb. 10 (box 5) 1967 Feb. 21 (box 5) 1967 Mar. 7 (box 5) 1967 Apr. 3 (box 5) 1967 Jun. 8 (box 5) 1967 Jul. 17 (box 5) 1967 Aug. 10 (box 5) 1967 Oct. 16 (box 5) 1968 Jan. 3 (box 2) 1968 Jan. 5 (box 5) 1968 Jan. 26 (box 5) 1968 Mar. 23 (box 5) 1968 Apr. 3 (box 5) 1968 May 13 (box 5) 1968 Aug. 8 (box 2) 1969 Jan. 3 (box 2) 1969 Feb. 7 (box 2) 1969 Feb. 10 (box 2) 1969 Apr. 3 (box 5) 1969 Oct. (box 2) 1969 Nov. 4 (box 5) 1974 Oct. 7 (box 2) 1974 Oct. 16 (box 6) 1975 May 27 (box 2) 1976 Apr. 12 (box 2) 1976 Apr. 20 (box 6) 1977 Aug. 17 (box 2) 1981 Nov. 11 (box 2) 1981 Nov. 16 (box 2) 1982 Apr. 16 (box 2) 1984 Jan. 9 (box 2) 1984 Jul. 18 (box 2) 1984 Aug. 28 (box 2) 1984 Nov. 27 (box 2)
Luke, Robert A. * - Florida State University / Correspondence 1967 Feb. 6 (box 5) 1968 Jan. 3 (box 5) 1968 Feb. 13 (box 5) 1968 Apr. 12 (box 5) 1968 Jun. 21 (box 5) 1968 Jul. 1 (box 5) 1968 Aug. 2 (box 5) 1968 Sep. 3 (box 5) 1969 Aug. 6 (box 2) 1970 May 15 (box 2) 1970 May 21 (box 5) 1970 Aug. 5 (box 5) 1970 Sep. 9 (box 2) 1970 Dec. 23 (box 2) 1977 Jan. 4 (box 6) 1977 Jun. 30 (box 4) 1977 Jul. 7 (box 6) 1979 Dec. 5 (box 4) 1980 Feb. 12 (box 6) 1980 May 16 (box 6) 1981 Nov. 4 (box 4) 1981 Nov. 22 (box 4) 1981 Dec. 30 (box 4) 1982 May 15 (box 4) 1982 Jul. 7 (box 4) 1982 Sep. 19 (box 4)
McClusky, Howard Y. - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Commission of Professors of Adult Education / Correspondence 1965 Nov. 17-18 (box 1)
McClusky, Howard Y. - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Correspondence. general 1970 Nov. 16 (box 1)
McClusky, Howard Y. - Florida State University / Correspondence 1970 Feb. 9 (box 2) 1976 Apr. 8 (box 6) 1976 Apr. 28 (box 4)
McClusky, Howard Y. - Florida State University / Institute on Education for Older Citizens / Correspondence 1972 Mar. 9 (box 7) 1972 Mar. 10 (box 7) 1972 Mar. 31 (box 7) 1972 Apr. 5 (box 7) 1972 Apr. 24 (box 7) 1972 Apr. 25 (box 7) 1972 May 10 (box 7) 1973 Jan. 10 (box 7) 1973 Feb. 8 (box 7) 1974 Feb. 18 (box 7)
McGovern, Sen. George - Florida State University / Institute on Education for Older Citizens / Correspondence 1972 Jan. 26 (box 7)
Muskie, Sen. Edmund - Florida State University / Institute on Education for Older Citizens / Correspondence 1972 Jan. 26 (box 7)
Pagano, Jules - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Commission of Professors of Adult Education / Correspondence 1970 Sep. 3 (box 1) 1970 Nov. 4 (box 1)
Pagano, Jules - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Correspondence, general 1969 Nov. 21 (box 1) 1969 Dec. 17 (box 1) 1969 Dec. 23 (box 1) 1969 Dec. 30 (box 1) 1970 Feb. 6 (box 1) 1970 Feb. 9 (box 1) 1970 Feb. 13 (box 1) 1970 Feb. 24 (box 1) 1970 Mar. 2 (box 1) 1970 Mar. 12 (box 1) 1970 Apr. 7 (box 1) 1970 Apr. 23 (box 1) 1970 Apr. 29 (box 1) 1970 Apr. 30 (box 1) 1970 Jun. 8 (box 1) 1970 Jun. 9 (box 1) 1970 Jun. 17 (box 1) 1970 Jun. 20 (box 1) 1970 Jun. 27 (box 1) 1970 Jul. 14 (box 1) 1970 Jul. 27 (box 1) 1970 Jul. 30 (box 1) 1970 Aug. (box 1) 1970 Aug. 3 (box 1) 1970 Aug. 31 (box 1) 1970 Sep. 9 (box 1) 1970 Sep. 14 (box 1) 1970 Sep. 23 (box 1) 1970 Sep. 25 (box 1) 1970 Oct. 9 (box 1) 1970 Oct. 12 (box 1) 1970 Oct. 22 (box 1) 1970 Nov. 9 (box 1) 1970 Nov. 16 (box 1) 1971 Apr. 19 1971 Apr. 26
Pagano, Jules - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Handbook of Adult Education / Correspondence 1970 Oct. 13 (box 2)
Pagano, Jules - Florida State University / Correspondence 1967 Mar. 6 (box 2) 1968 Mar. 8 (box 5) 1968 Apr. 12 (box 5) 1970 Jan. 22 (box 2) 1970 Apr. 9 (box 2) 1970 Jun. 11 (box 2) 1971 Feb. 12 (box 5) 1971 Feb. 19 (box 5) 1971 Apr. 29 (box 5) 1971 Jun. 29 (box 2) 1971 Sep. 16 (box 2) 1972 May 15 (box 6) 1972 Jun. 7 (box 6) 1972 Dec. 20 (box 6) 1973 Apr. 4 (box 3) 1973 Apr. 26 (box 3) 1973 Aug. 16 (box 6) 1973 Aug. 28 (box 6) 1973 Oct. 23 (box 6) 1974 Mar. 15 (box 3) 1974 May 9 (box 3) 1974 May 15 (box 3) 1976 Nov. 12 (box 4) 1977 Jul. 25 (box 6) 1977 Aug. 24 (box 4)
Qazilbush, Husain - Florida State University / Correspondence 1967 Mar. 6 (box 5) 1967 Mar. 24 (box 5) 1967 Mar. 28 (box 5) 1968 Feb. 16 (box 5) 1968 Apr. 1 (box 5) 1968 Aug. 2 (box 5) 1970 Apr. 3 (box 5) 1970 Jun. 26 (box 5) 1970 Dec. 23 (box 5) 1972 Nov. 8 (box 3) 1973 Apr. 19 (box 3) 1973 May 9 (box 6) 1973 May 18 (box 6) 1973 May 22 (box 3) 1973 May 23 (box 6) 1973 Jun. 13 (box 6) 1973 Jul. 20 (box 3) 1973 Jul. 5 (box 3) 1973 Aug. 6 (box 6) 1973 Sep. 26 (box 3) 1973 Oct. 10 (box 3) 1973 Oct. 25 (box 3) 1973 Nov. 13 (box 6) 1973 Nov. 21 (box 3) 1974 Jan. 16 (box 6) 1974 Mar. 18 (box 3) 1974 Apr. 2 (box 6) 1974 Aug. 27 (box 3) 1974 Nov. 20 (box 3) 1974 Dec. 11 (box 3) 1974 Dec. 17 (box 3) 1975 Jan. 8 (box 6) 1975 Jan. 24 (box 4) 1975 Feb. 19 (box 4) 1975 Feb. 25 (box 6) 1975 Mar. 26 (box 4) 1975 Sep. 17 (box 6) 1975 Oct. 22 (box 4) 1976 Jan. 21 (box 4) 1976 Aug. 30 (box 6) 1976 Sep. 29 (box 4) 1976 Oct. 4 (box 6) 1976 Nov. 8 (box 4) 1978 Apr. 14 (box 4) 1978 May 16 (box 6) 1979 Feb. 26 (box 4) 1980 Apr. 1 (box 4) 1982 Feb. 18 (box 4) 1982 Mar. 9 (box 4)
Rusk, Dean - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Correspondence, general 1970 Jan. 21 (box 1)
Sharer, Robert E. * - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Correspondence, general 1968 Jul. 18 (box 1) 1968 Aug. 1 (box 1) 1968 Oct. 17 (box 1) 1968 Nov. 27 (box 1) 1969 Feb. 12 (box 1) 1969 Feb. 27 (box 1) (2 letters) 1969 Mar. 18 (box 1) 1969 Mar. 19 (box 1) 1969 Mar. 25 (box 1) 1969 Apr. 8 (box 1) 1969 Apr. 16 (box 1) 1969 Apr. 24 (box 1) 1969 May 25 (box 1) 1969 Jun. 4 (box 1) 1969 Jun. 9 (box 1) 1969 Jun. 13 (box 1) 1969 Jun. 25 (box 1) 1969 Jul. 11 (box 1) 1969 Jul. 29 (box 1) (2 letters) 1969 Jul. 30 (box 1) 1969 Jul. 31 (box 1) 1969 Aug. 1 (box 1) 1969 Aug. 4 (box 1) 1969 Aug. 6 (box 1) 1969 Sep. 9 (box 1) 1969 Oct. 21 (box 1) (2 letters) 1969 Sep. 17 (box 1) 1969 Oct. 2 (box 1) 1969 Oct. 9 (box 1) 1969 Oct. 17 (box 1) 1969 Oct. 21 (box 1) (2 letters) 1969 Oct. 29 (box 1) (2 letters) 1969 Oct. 31 (box 1) 1969 Nov. 7 (box 1) 1969 Dec. 17 (box 1) 1969 Dec. 19 (box 1) 1969 Dec. 23 (box 1) 1970 Jun. 20 (box 1)
Sharer, Robert E. * - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Handbook of Adult Education / Correspondence 1968 Nov. 26 (box 2) 1969 Jan. 23 (box 2) (box 2) 1969 Jan. 28 (box 2) (2 letters) 1969 Feb. 3 (box 2) 1969 Feb. 4 (box 2) 1969 Feb. 6 (box 2) 1969 Feb. 10 (box 2) 1969 Feb. 26 (box 2) 1969 Jul. 11 (box 2) 1969 Aug. 12 (box 2) 1969 Sep. 11 (box 2)
Sharer, Robert E. * - Florida State University / Correspondence 1967 Dec. 20 (box 5) 1969 Mar. 18 (box 5) 1969 May 1 (box 5) 1969 May 2 (box 5) 1969 May 9 (box 5) 1969 Oct. 21 (box 5) 1971 Jul. 24 (box 2)
Sheats, Paul H. * - Florida State University / Correspondence 1976 Jun. 9 (box 6) 1976 Jun. 30 (box 4) 1980 Feb. 12 (box 6) 1980 May 16 (box 6) 1980 Nov. 1 (box 4) 1980 Dec. 15 (box 4) 1982 Jun. (box 4) 1982 Jun. 9 (box 4)
Snyder Robert E. - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Commission of Professors of Adult Education / Correspondence 1971 Oct. 13 (box 1)
Snyder Robert E. - Florida State University / Correspondence 1967 Apr. 27 (box 5) 1967 May 15 (box 5) 1967 May 29 (box 5) 1967 Jun. 1 (box 5) 1968 Feb. 23 (box 5) 1968 Sep. 20 (box 5) 1969 Jun. 27 (box 5) 1969 Nov. 17 (box 5) 1970 Aug. (box 5) 1970 Aug. 6 (box 5) 1971 Jan. 14 (box 5) 1971 Feb. 25 (box 5) 1973 Feb. 1 (box 3) 1973 Mar. 9 (box 6) 1974 Mar. 5 (box 3) 1976 Jun. (box 4)
Snyder Robert E. - Florida State University / Institute on Education for Older Citizens 1972 Jan. 26 (box 7)
Stensland, Per G. * - Florida State University / Correspondence 1967 Jan. 6 (box 5)
Thiede, Wilson B. - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. / Commission of Professors of Adult Education / Correspondence 1967 Mar. 3 (box 1) 1971 Oct. 13 (box 1)